kinonation.com 2019-02-22

# Filmhub | Privacy Policy

When you use Filmhub you are trusting us with your information. We understand that this is a big responsibility and work hard to protect your information. This privacy policy sets out how Filmhub uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. Filmhub is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Filmhub may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Personal Information. This is information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email, and address
  * Business Information. This is information that identifies a company that you are associated with, such as company name, company address
  * Payment Information. This is information that we need in order to pay you. This includes information such as taxpayer identification, country of residence, and PayPal account. Only you can update your Payment Information.
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers, such your personal interest and preferences that you provide to us.

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes.

We will never sell your information.

### Managing, Reviewing, and Updating your information

When you are signed in, you will be able to review and update your information.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide when visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by [contacting us](https://intercom.help/filmhub).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please [contact us](https://intercom.help/filmhub).

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### About Us

Filmhub is the name used by Kinonation, Inc. a Delaware corporation.
